The Amanda Seale Show.
Things I learned this week, yeah.
Did you know that there were no black videos shown on MTV
when it launched as a matter of policy?
Like it wasn't just like, you know,
we're just not into black music.
Like their policy was we're not playing black videos
because they were more so like featured
in the Bible Belt when they first launched
and they just didn't want people to be scared.
Do you know what the first black video was on MTV?
Wasn't it Michael Jackson Thriller or something like that?
I thought it was Billie Jean.
And that is actually incorrect.
It was musical youth past the duchy ponder left hand side.
I say, give me the music, make me jump on front.
Did you know that bees don't buzz during an eclipse?
Stuff like that be like creepy, but fascinating.
So using tiny microphones suspended among flowers,
researchers recorded the buzzing of bees
during the 2017 North American eclipse.
The bees were active and noisy
right up to the last moments before totality.
As totality hit, the bees all went silent.
Son, what are the bees trying to tell us?
Did you know that your zip code tells information
in the numbers in like a very specific way?
America is split up into nine sections.
So the first number is the section.
The second two numbers are the city.
The last two numbers is your actual post office.
Things we learned this week.
Yeah.
We are.